Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory3 Mss.B.B61.inventory03
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents C
  - Cattell, J. McKeen (Box 15)
    - To Seligman, E.R.A., 1917 June 13 and June 16
    - To Seligman, E.R.A., 1917 June 23
    - To Woodbridge, F.J.E., 1918 Nov. 25; 2p
    - To Young, A.A., 1917 Nov. 11; 9p
    - From Boas, E.P., 1943 Mar. 3
    - From Gregory, T.W., 1918 July 8
    - From Holmes, W.W., 1927 Nov. 29
    - From Pine, J.B., 1918 Apr. 3; 1p
    - From Rives, G.L., 1913 May 21
    - From Roos, C.F., 1932 Nov. 14
    - From Roos, C.F., 1932 Nov. 20
    - From Seligman, E.R.A., 1917 May 14
    - From Seligman, E.R.A., 1917 June 5
    - From Seligman, E.R.A., 1917 June 14
    - From Seligman, E.R.A., 1917 June 18
    - From Taggart, J., 1917 Feb. 23
  - Cattell, Owen (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1917 July 30
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 1p
  - Cattell, Wm. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 30
    - From Boas, 1931 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 1; 1p
  - Caturegli, A. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1917 May 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 30
  - Caulkins, E.D. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1914 July 28
  - Celler, Emanuel (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 2 and Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 21; 1p
      enc. U.S. Congress, House
      - re aliens admission for permanent residence, 1938 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Dickstein, S., 1938 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Dickstein, S., 1938 Apr. 13
  - Centeno, A. (Box 15)
    - see FB open letter, culture & democ. in Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Central Com., Relief, Distress, Germany, Austria (Box 15)
    see Waltz, John A.
  - Centralblatt für Anthropologie (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 27; 1p
  - Chaddock, R.E. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 5; 1p
  - Chadwick, F.E. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 12
  - Chalfant, F.H. (Box 15)
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Apr. 1
  - Chamberlain, A.F. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1901 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 28
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1890 June 9
    - To Boas, 1890 June 18
    - To Boas, 1894 June 21
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1897 Aug. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1901 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1901 Feb. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 June 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1913 July 7
    - To Boas, 1913 July 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 8
  - Chamberlain, E.E. (Box 15)
    - To Bielaski, A.B., 1918 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Walcott, C.D., 1918 Jan. 4; 1p
  - Chamberlain, Joseph C. or P. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 31; 3p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 13; 1p
    - see Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Murphy, Roy D., 1941 Feb. 17
  - Chamberlain, T.C. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p
  - Chamberlain, W.B. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 18; 1p
  - Chambers, Robt. (Box 15)
    - see FB Open letter, Spain, Replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Champion, Martha (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 1; 2p
      - receipt, 1935 Feb.
      - receipt, 1935 Mar.
      - receipt, 1935 May
      - receipt, 1935 June 7
    - To Boas, 1935 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 24; 1p
    - To Benedict, R.F., 1935 July 3; 1p
  - Champion, Pierre (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 2; 1p
  - Chandlee, Wm. H. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 4
  - Chandler (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1905 Sep. 23
  - Chandler, R.H. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 17
  - Chandler, W.J. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 8; 1p
  - Chang, Chentung Liang (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 7; 1p
  - Changes in Attitude with Questionnaire --, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Channing, Edward (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 5; 1p
  - Chanquet, G.G. (Box 15)
    - see Kroeber, A.L., 1928 Dec. 4
  - Chapin, E. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 16; 1p
  - Chapin, F. Stuart (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 3; 1p
  - Chapman (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
  - Chapman, Abraham or E. (Box 15)
    - 1905 Apr. 13, 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 26; 1p
    - To Martin-Dillon, P.R., 1939 May 23
    - open letter, 1939 May 26
  - Chapman, John W. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1910 May 31
    - From Boas, 1910 July 26
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 28
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 May 16
    - To Boas, 1911 June 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1914 July 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 15
  - Chapman, K.M. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 18; 1p
  - Chapman, May L. (Box 15)
    - To Boas, 1911 July 27
  - Chapman, O.L. (Box 15)
    - From Boas re Barrows, A., 1939 Mar. 24
  - Charis, Elena Aguilar (Box 15)
    - To Jalisco, Gobernador), 1911 Dec. 16; 3p
  - Chase, Harry Woodburn (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Aug. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 3; 1p
    - Memo re Dr. Geo. Saslow enc. with Cattell, McKeen, 1936 Sep. 22; 3p
  - Chatelain, V.E. (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 28; 1p
  - Chavez, Ezequiel A. (Box 15-16)
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 31; 2p
    - see FB to Gordon, G.B., 1910 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 17; 2p
    - see FB to Butler, N.M., 1910 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 21and15
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 6; 2p
    - see FB to Dixon, R.B., 1911 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 25; 2p
    - also to Seler, Gordon, Huntington & Dixon, 1911 Feb. 28and4
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1911 May 11
    - From Boas, 1911 May 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 June 8; 4p
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Sept. 11 and Oct. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 6; 2p
    - also see Seler, E., 1913 Feb. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 7; 1p
    - also to Seler, Dixon, Gordon, Butler, 1913 Aug. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 6 and Sep. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 30; 2p
    - also see FB to Engerrand, G.C., 1913 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 12 and Sep. 25
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1916 May 11
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 31 and Oct. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 11; 3p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 May 7
    - From Boas, 1917 July 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 1 & 21
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 15; 4p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1910 July 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1913 July 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 May 9
    - To Boas, 1914 May 12
    - To Boas, 1914 June 10
    - To Boas, 1914 July 27
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1916 May 4
    - To Boas, 1916 May 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 May 11
    - To Boas, 1916 May 29
    - To Boas, 1916 July 3
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 12; 7p
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 23; 5p
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 11; 2p
    - (activities and publications), 1916 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 11; 5p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 12
    - To Boas, 1917 June 21; 5p
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 7 & Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 14; 6p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 4; 1p
    - From E_____, 1911 Jan. 13
    - To Sec'y, InstrucciC3n pC:blica y bellas artes, Mexico, 1913 Aug. 19; 2p
  - Chavez, Leticia (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec.
  - Chavez Orozco, L. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p
  - Chelio, R.M. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 13; 1p
  - Chemical Abstracts (Box 16)
    see Crane, E.J.
  - Chenaid, G. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 24
  - Chentung Liang Chang (Box 16)
    (Chinese Min. to U.S.)
    - From Boas, 1904 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Chief of Imperial Chinese Customs, 1904 Nov. 18; 1p
    - To Mr. Foord, 1904 Oct. 7; 1p
  - Cherniavsky, L. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Chertak, D. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 9; 1p
  - Chesney (Box 16)
    - (U.S. Bureau Ethnology), 1887 Sep. 16
  - Chesnut, V.K. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1893 June 25; 1p
  - Chester, F.D. (Box 16)
    - To Keppel, F.P., 1906 Aug. 14
  - Chetelat, Eleanor Beer (Box 16)
    (same as Beer, E.F.?)
    - To Boas, 1928 July 25; 3p
  - Chevier, J. and P.V. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1916 July 11
    - To Boas, 1916 July 13
  - Chevigny, Hector (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 10; 2p
  - Chevrier, M.P. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1916 July 28
    - To Boas, 1916 July 31
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 June 2
    - To Boas, 1917 June 22
  - Chicago, Univ. of (Box 16)
    - From Lyon, E.P., 1901 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Peace Committee, 1938 Apr. 19; 1p
  - Chicago, Univ. Press (Box 16)
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from FB, 1902 Sep. 4; 1p
  - Chicago World's Fair (Box 16)
    - Tentative, anthrop. sec., 1930 Dec. 31; [?]
  - Childe, V.G. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 27; 1p
  - Children's Aid (Box 16)
    see Van Ness, Elise
  - Childs (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 14
  - Chilis, N. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
  - Chin, Henry P. (Box 16)
    - To Gaston-Heye, H., 1940 Dec.; 1p
  - Chinard, Gilbert (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p
  - Chlinitz [?], F. von (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1885 May 20
  - Choate, J.H. (Box 16)
    - see Schwab, G.H., 1906 May 26
  - Chockalongam Pillai, V. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 21; 2p
    - To?, 1936 Sep. 21; 1p
  - Chrewich (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 18
  - Christian,? (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 19; 6p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 14; 2p
  - Christian, C. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p
  - Christian, V. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 27; 1p
  - Christian Front (Box 16)
    - To Jackson, R.H., 1939 Dec.; 3p
  - Christiernin, Charles L. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 4; 1p
  - Chronicle, -- The (N.Y.) (Box 16)
    - 1917 Aug. 15
  - Chrysler, Walter P. Jr. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 30; 1p
  - Chubb, Thomas Caldecott (Box 16)
    - From Mason, Gregory, 1941 Sep. 18
  - Church, Franklin H. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 10; 1p
      - enc. to Mills, C.A., 1936 Oct. 3; 2p
  - Churchill, Alfred Vance (Box 16)
    - see FB open letter, Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Churchill, M. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Chwatal, H. (Box 16)
    - To Ravené, G., 1889 Nov. 26; 4p
  - Cillis, Hubert (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 11
    - see Schwab, G.H., 1906 May 26
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 10; 1p
  - Cipriani, L. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 26; 2p
  - Ciro, J. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 22; 1p
  - Clair (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 27
  - Clark, A.H. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov.; 1p
    - To Day, A.L., 1931 May 19
      - enc. with Roos, C.F., 1931 May 20
  - Clark, Mrs. C.C. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 21; 12p
  - Clark, C.P. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 5; 4p
  - Clark, D.W. (Box 16)
    - To Deloria, E.C., 1930 Nov. 6; 2p
      - enc. with E.C., 1930 Nov. 9
  - Clark, E.W. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1929 June 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 3; 1p
  - Clark, Felice (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 10; 1p
  - Clark, G.H. (Box 16)
    - Report enc. with Fairbairn, A.M.D., 1931 Feb. 2
  - Clark, Helen (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 3
  - Clark, J.P. (Box 16)
    - To Hayden, P.M., 1934 May 14; 2p
      - enc. with above to Columbia U. Council, 1934 May 15
  - Clark, Walter (Box 16)
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Apr. 1
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Apr. 27
  - Clark University (Box 16)
    - Controversy, 1892
    - Second decennial, 1909 May 15; 3p
      Could not locate (in Papers as on Film) 5/9/80
  - Clark Univ. Press (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 2; 1p
  - Clarke, A.H. (Box 16)
    - From Fleming, J.A., 1931 June 6
  - Clarke, C.P. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 2
  - Clarke, H.T. (Box 16)
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
  - Clarke, J.J. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
  - Clarke, J.M. (Box 16)
    - 1913 From Boas, 1913 Feb. 26
    - 1913 From Boas, 1914 Mar. 20
    - 1913 From Boas, 1914 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 31
  - Clarke, T.R. (Box 16)
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Apr. 28
  - Classen, Arthur (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 1p
  - Classical Journal, U. of Chicago Press (Box 16)
    See Miller, Frank J.
  - Clauss (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 28
  - Claussen (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1932 July 13; 1p
  - Clawson, W.H. (Box 16)
    - From Barbeau, C.M., 1918 June 8; 2p
  - Claxton, P.P. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 28
  - Clay, Albert T. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 29; 2p
  - Clay, S.T. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 7; 1p
  - Clay, Walter W. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 11; 1p
  - Clayton, J.B. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1907 May 22
    - To Boas, 1907 July 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 June 17
  - Clemens, James B. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 30; 1p
  - Clement, A. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Clements, H.S. (Box 16)
    - From Nowell, C.J., 1915 Jan. 28
  - Clements, W. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 26; 1p
  - Cleveland, Treadwell (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 5; 1p
  - Cliffiside Park, Mayor & Council (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 May 22; 2p
  - Clinchy, E.R. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 24; 1p
  - Clothier, R.C. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 4
  - Clough, B.C. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 16; 1p
  - Coane, C.B. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 13
  - Cody, H.J. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 3
  - Coe, Ada M. (Box 16)
    - See Replies, Spain, F. Boas, 1938 Jan.
  - Coe, D.P. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 10
  - Coe, G.A. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 16; 2p
  - Coffee, John M. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9
    - To Boas, 1938 June 13
    - To Boas, 1940 Sep. 17
  - Coffin, Henry S. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Turner, Lily, 1941 Mar. 19; 1p
      - enc. with Rautenstrauch, 1941 Mar. 21
  - Cohan, H. (Box 16)
    - see Wendiner[?], H.G., 1929 Dec. 20
  - Cohen, A.M. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Cohen, Bertha, 1931 Aug. 5; 1p (Box 16)
    - 1931 Aug. 17, 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 4; 2p
  - Cohen, Felix S. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 15; 1p
  - Cohen, Frances (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1908 June 5
  - Cohen, George W. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 11; 1p
  - Cohen, J. (Box 16)
    - To Augustin, J.J., 1941 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Cohen, L.B. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 26; 2p
  - Cohen, Martin (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 24; 1p.
  - Cohen, Morris R. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 22; 1p
    - See FB Open letter, Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
    - See Weiner, Philip Paul, 1938 Nov. 30
  - Cohen, Mrs. M.R. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 10; 1p
  - Cohen, Max M. [?] (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 11; 1p
  - Cohen, Percy V. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 19
  - Cohen, Samuel (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 7; 1p
  - Cohn. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 3
  - Cohn, Mrs. (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 9; 1p
  - Cohn, Alfred E. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Cohn, Samuel (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 8; 1p
  - Cohn, Stewart (Box 16)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 1
  - Colby, F.M. (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 24
  - Cole, F.C. [Fay Cooper] (Box 16)
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 16
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 27; 1p